<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Joseph B. LeRoy</title><link>https://josephbleroy.com/</link><description>Recent content on Joseph B. LeRoy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://josephbleroy.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Implementing HTTPS and HTTP Headers in Nginx</title><link>https://josephbleroy.com/posts/2017/01/implementing-https-and-http-headers-in-nginx/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://josephbleroy.com/posts/2017/01/implementing-https-and-http-headers-in-nginx/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s been a lot of focus on internet security and encryption over the past several years. You&amp;rsquo;ll find dozens of news reports every day about companies getting breached, individuals having their bank accounts compromised, and security researchers finding vulnerabilities in web services and encryption protocols.
As someone who is passionate about security and technology, I&amp;rsquo;ve been driven to keep up with current standards and implement best practices so that I don&amp;rsquo;t become victim to preventable vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title>The Current State of DevOps and the Agile Movement in Japan</title><link>https://josephbleroy.com/posts/2016/09/the-current-state-of-devops-and-the-agile-movement-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://josephbleroy.com/posts/2016/09/the-current-state-of-devops-and-the-agile-movement-in-japan/</guid><description>Last Friday I was fortunate enough to attend a seminar at Creationline, Inc. in the Akihabara district of Tokyo. The topic, as you may have already figured out, was on the current state of DevOps and the Agile Movement in Japan. I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in learning more about how software development and projects are managed in Japan. Some of the speakers included Ippei Suzuki from Creationline, Inc., Hiroaki &amp;ldquo;bucci&amp;rdquo; Kawabuchi from CI&amp;amp;T and Tsuyoshi Ushio from Microsoft.</description></item><item><title>Packet Capture Analysis of Ransomware</title><link>https://josephbleroy.com/posts/2016/05/packet-capture-analysis-of-ransomware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://josephbleroy.com/posts/2016/05/packet-capture-analysis-of-ransomware/</guid><description>In the 2016 Data Breach Investigation Report, Verizon discovered that &amp;ldquo;ransomware is on the rise&amp;rdquo;. Malware crafted to encrypt the victim&amp;rsquo;s drive content, in lieu of a hefty Bitcoin payment to unlock the protected files, encompasses 39% of crimeware incidents in 2015. Hackers primarily targeted the public sector, manufacturing, and information industries. What makes ransomware so easy to deploy is the minimal skill set required to craft an executable file masked as something else, such as a gif or flash object.</description></item></channel></rss>